Guide to the Stephen Henry Schneider Papers SC1053
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Conferences, Meetings, and Professional Travel, Series 6
  - Oceans in the New Millenium: Critical Issues: Monterey, CA, March 2000 (Box 162, Folder 22)
  - Winslow Foundation: India and Bhutan Wildlife Field Trip: India and Bhutan, March-April 2000 (Box 162, Folder 23)
  - IGCC: Instituting the Kyoto Protocol: La Jolla, CA, April 2000 (Box 162, Folder 24)
  - Wallace Stegner Environmental Center: Global Warming: San Francisco, CA, May 2000 (Box 162, Folder 25)
  - GAIA 2000: 2nd Chapman Conf. on the Gaia Hypothesis: Valencia, Spain, June 2000 (Box 162, Folder 26)
  - Science and Technology: Thinking the Future @ Expo 2000: Hanover, Germany, July 2000 (Box 162, Folder 27)
  - Matrix Workshop on Scaling Issues: Maastricht, the Netherlands, July 2000 (Box 162, Folder 28)
  - Pew Center on Global Climate Change Meeting: Washington D.C., July 2000 (Box 162, Folder 29)
  - NBER/Yale Center Workshop: Societal Impacts of Abrupt Climate Change: Snowmass, CO, July 2000 (Box 162, Folder 30)
  - Community Office for Resource Efficiency (CORE) Earth Day Debate: Aspen, CO, July 2000 (Box 162, Folder 31)
  - IPCC/TAR/WG2 Lead Authors Meeting: Lisbon, July-August 2000 (Box 162, Folder 32)
  - CSIRO: 5th International Conference on Greenhouse Gas Control Technologies: Cairns, Australia, August 2000 (Box 162, Folder 33)
  - Jerry Mahlman Retirement: Beyond the Science of Climate Change: Princeton, NJ, September 2000 (Box 162, Folder 34)
  - Bates College: Muskie Environmental Lecture - Lewiston, ME, April 1994 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - SSRC/GEC Committee Mtg. - New York, NY, 21-22 April 1994 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - PEW Scholars Program Selection Committee Mtg. - Philadelphia, PA, May 1994 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Development Team/ National 4-H/ Honda North America - Estas Park, CO, May 1997 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Chapman Conference on the Gaia Hypothesis - Valencia, Spain (1/2), 2000 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Chapman Conference on the Gaia Hypothesis - Valencia, Spain (2/2), 2000 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Globalization Conference - Stanford, July 2001 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - SHS & TLR Australia Residency (corr., etc), 2006 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Adelaide Thinkers in Residence packet & correspondence, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - Finger Lakes Institute Conference - Geneva, N.Y., 2007 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - Justice in Adaptation to Climate Change - Norwich, UK, September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - EPA - Institute of Medicine online "uncertainty" meetings, 2007 (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, Doomsday Clock Symposium- New York, NY, January 2010 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - Latin School Ethics Program talk, AMS Warren Washington Symposium, Eugene Visit - Chicago, Atlanta, Eugene, January 2010 (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - World Economic Forum - Davos, Switzerland (1 of 6), January 2010 (Box 171, Folder 15)
  - World Economic Forum - Davos, Switzerland (2 of 6), January 2010 (Box 171, Folder 16)
  - World Economic Forum - Davos, Switzerland (3 of 6), January 2010 (Box 171, Folder 17)
  - World Economic Forum - Davos, Switzerland (4 of 6), January 2010 (Box 171, Folder 18)
  - World Economic Forum - Davos, Switzerland (5 of 6), January 2010 (Box 171, Folder 19)
  - World Economic Forum - Davos, Switzerland (6 of 6), January 2010 (Box 171, Folder 20)
  - AAAS 2010 Annual Meeting - San Diego, CA, February 2010 (Box 171, Folder 21)
  - Asilomar Conference on Climate Intervention Technologies - Pacific Grove, CA, March 2010 (Box 171, Folder 22)
  - 3rd Annual Center for Corporate Citizenship & Sustainability Conference - Milpitas, CA, March 2010 (Box 171, Folder 23)
  - UC Merced Sigma Xi Spring Symposium - Merced, CA, April 2010 (Box 171, Folder 24)
  - Turning the Tide - Fort Baker, CA, April 2010 (Box 171, Folder 25)
  - National Academy of Sciences Board Meeting & Earth Day Rally - Washington, D.C., April 2010 (Box 171, Folder 26)
  - UN Association Sonoma County Chapter lecture & Wine Country trip, April 2010 (Box 171, Folder 27)
  - University of Kansas Visit (Book Tour) - Lawrence, KS, May 2010 (Box 171, Folder 28)
  - National Geographic Society: Great Energy Challenge - Washington D.C., May 2010 (Box 171, Folder 29)
  - University of Waterloo Walter Bean Visiting Professorship - Waterloo, Ontario, Canada, May 2010 (Box 171, Folder 30)
  - NAS Standing Committee on Social Science Evidence Use meeting - Washington D.C., May 2010 (Box 171, Folder 31)
  - July 4th Weekend Trip - Eugene, OR, July 2010 (Box 171, Folder 32)
  - IPCC Cross-Working Group Meeting on Uncertainties - Stanford, CA, July 2010 (Box 171, Folder 33)
  - 17th ISA World Congress of Sociology - Goteborg, Sweden, July 2010 (Box 171, Folder 34)
  - Aspen Environment FOrum - Aspen, CO, July 2010 (Box 171, Folder 35)
  - Science Foo Camp (did not attend), July-August 2010 (Box 171, Folder 36)
  - IPCC/ARS Synthesis Report Scoping Meeting - Liege, Belgium (did not attend), August 2010 (Box 171, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: Fellow of the California Academy of Sciences (Box 171, Folder 38)
  - Canadian Boreal Initiative, George River, Canada (did not attend), August 2010 (Box 171, Folder 39)
  - 2nd Agilent Technical Conference - San Francisco, CA (did not attend), November 2010 (Box 171, Folder 40)
  - Adelaide, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 41)
  - Thinker file, Adelaide, 2008 (Box 171, Folder 42)
  - American Institute of Biological Sciences (AIBS), Mauna Loa, HI, Aug. 1992 (Box 183, Item 1-2)
  - PEWS Scholars Program in Conservation and the Environment annual meeting, Timberline Lodge, OR, Oct. 1992 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Carroll College Distinguished Lecture. Waukesha, WI, Nov. 1992 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Tom Donahue Symposium, Ann Arbor, MI, Nov. 1992 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Mathematical Ecology Workshop, Trieste, Italy, Nov. 1992 (Box 183, Item 6-7)
  - SSRC: Cmte. for Research on Global Environmental Change, Pinehurst, NC, Nov. 1992 (Box 183, Item 8-9)
  - SSRC: Cmte. for Research on Global Environmental Change, New York, NY, Apr. 1994 (Box 183, Item 10-11)
  - Human Dimensions of Global Environmental Change Community, 1st open meeting, Durham, NC, June 1995 (Box 183, Item 12-13)
  - EFIEA Policy Workshop: Scaling Issues in Integrated Assessment, Mechelen, the Netherlands, July 2000 (Box 183, Folder 14)
  - Second Globalization Forum, Sanya City, China, Jan. 2001 (Box 183, Folder 15)
  - Market Solutions to Climate Change Conference, Washington, D.C. & Stanford, CA, Sept. 2001 (Box 183, Folder 16)
  - Bluewater Network/ San Jose Global Warming Town Hall meeting, San Jose, CA, Dec. 2001 (Box 183, Folder 17)
  - American Geophysical Union (AGU) Fall meeting, San Francisco, CA, Dec. 2001 (Box 183, Item 18-19)
  - Energy Modeling Forum (EMF) Workshop on Critical Issues in Climate Change, Snowmass, CO, July 2004 (Box 183, Item 20-21)
  - Climate Institute: Board Meeting [draft agenda], Washington, D.C., Mar. 2005 (Box 183, Folder 22)
  - Primary Industries & Resources South Australia (PIRSA), Sydney, Australia, 2006 (Box 183, Folder 23)
  - Australian Climate Change Research Centre, 2006 (Box 183, Folder 24)
  - South Australia, 2006 (Box 183, Folder 25)
  - South Australia Water, 2006 (Box 183, Folder 26)
  - California Research Bureau (CRB) talk, Sacramento, CA, Oct. 2006 (Box 183, Folder 27)
  - American Geophysical Union (AGU) Fall meeting, San Francisco, CA, 2007 (Box 183, Folder 28)
  - Dahlem Workshop on Atmospheric Chemstry, Berlin, Germany, May 1982 (Box 182, Item 1-2)
  - Travel vouchers for SHS 1990 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - MIT technology day, Cambridge, MA, June 1990 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Aspen Institute n Global Change, Aspen, CO, July 1990 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Federation of American Scientist annual meeting, Washington, D.C., Dec. 1990 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Forest Service Workshop, Boulder, CO, Sept. 1990 (Box 182, Item 7-8)
  - SSRC committee, Boston, MA, Jan. 1991 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - OIES, 8th Steering Committee meeting, Boulder, CO, Jan. 1990 (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - AAAS session (with Warren Hern), Washington, D.C., Feb. 1991 (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Smithsonian meeting, Washington, D.C., Mar. 1992 (Box 182, Folder 12)
  - Technologies for a Greenhouse Constrained Society, Oak Ridge, TN, June 1991 (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - CEQ Roundtable,Boulder, CO, June 1991 (Box 182, Folder 14)
  - Aspen Institue Executive Seminar, Aspen, CO, June 1991 (Box 182, Folder 15)
  - Aspen Global Change Institue, Aspen, CO, July 1991 (Box 182, Folder 16)
  - American Ornithologists Union, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, Aug. 1991 (Box 182, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Centennial Roundtable, Stanford, CA, Sept. 1991 (Box 182, Folder 18)
  - NSF Workshop on Global Change, Friday Harbor, WA, Sept. 1991 (Box 182, Folder 19)
  - SSRC meeting, New York, Oct. 1991 (Box 182, Folder 20)
  - Dahlem Conference, Berlin, Germany, Dec. 1991 (Box 182, Folder 21)
  - AAAS meeting, Chicago, IL, Feb. 1992 (Box 182, Folder 22)
  - Smithsonian Conference, Mar. 1992 (Box 182, Folder 23)
  - Joint Appeal, Washington, D.C., May 1992 (Box 182, Folder 24)
  - EMF Workshop on Climate Change Impacts and Integrated Assessment - Snowmass, CO (1/2), 1998 August 3-11 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - EMF Workshop on Climate Change Impacts and Integrated Assessment - Snowmass, CO (2/2), 1998 August 3-11 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Getting the Press Right: Can Tax Reform Help both the Economy and the Environment? - Palo Alto, 1997 May 21 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - EMF Workshop on Climate Change Impacts and Integrated Assessment - Snowmass, CO (1/2), 1999 July 26- August 5 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - EMF Workshop on Climate Change Impacts and Integrated Assessment - Snowmass, CO (2/2), 1999 July 26 - August 5 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Initiatives Workshop (1/2), 2004 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Initiatives Workshop (2/2), 2004 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Global Change Institute on Tace Gases and the Biosphere, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Global Change Institute on Explaining Records of Past Global Changes (1/2), 1989 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - Global Change Institute on Explaining Records of Past Global Changes (2/2), 1989 (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - Aspen Institute Executive Seminar Readings (1/2), undated (Box 195, Folder 11)
  - Aspen Institute Executive Seminar Readings (2/2), undated (Box 195, Folder 12)
  - Energy and Environment Directorate (1/2), 2001 (Box 195, Folder 13)
  - Energy and Environment Directorate (2/2), 2001 (Box 195, Folder 14)
  - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change (1/2), 2001 Nov 5-6 (Box 195, Folder 15)
  - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change (2/2), 2001 Nov 5-6 (Box 195, Folder 16)
  - Global Possible: World Resources Institute Conference - Queenstown, Maryland (1/3), 1984 May (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Global Possible: World Resources Institute Conference - Queenstown, Maryland (2/3), 1984 May (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Global Possible: World Resources Institute Conference - Queenstown, Maryland (3/3), 1984 May (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - TIME Environment Conference - Boulder, CO, 1988 Nov 10-12 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - UCAR: Climate Systems Modeling Initiative Workshop - Boulder, CO, 1989 January (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Office for Interdisciplinary Earth Studies (OIES) Steering Committee - 12th meeting - Boulder, CO, 1993 October 8 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Global Climate Change Workshop - Ypsilanti, MI, 1993 Dec 6-8 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Social Science Research Council (SSRC) meeting - New York, NY (1/2), 1995 October 12-13 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Research Council (SSRC) meeting - New York, NY (2/2), 1995 October 12-13 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - CGP United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change - Conference of the Parties - 6th session - The Hague (1/2), 2000 (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - CGP United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change - Conference of the Parties - 6th session - The Hague (2/2), 2000 (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change - Washington D.C., 2002 November (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change - Washington D.C., 2003 May (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change - Quebec, Canada, 2003 October (Box 204, Folder 14)
  - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change - Washington D.C., 2004 June 17-18 (Box 204, Folder 15)
  - Energy Modeling Forum (EMF): Critical Issues in Climate Change - Snowmass, CO (1/2), 2007 July/August (Box 204, Folder 16)
  - Energy Modeling Forum (EMF): Critical Issues in Climate Change - Snowmass, CO (2/2), 2007 July/August (Box 204, Folder 17)
  - Standing Committee on Social Science Evidence for Use - 1st meeting - Washington D.C. (1/2), 2007 April (Box 204, Folder 18)
  - Standing Committee on Social Science Evidence for Use - 1st meeting - Washington D.C. (2/2), 2007 April (Box 204, Folder 19)
  - Governor's Science and Technology Advisory Council - Denver, CO, 1980 July (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - AAAS meeting - Is nuclear Winter Real and Relevant? Strategic Implications, 1987 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - AAAS meeting - Nuclear Winter or Nuclear Fall? The Evolution of Climate Model, 1987 February (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Los Alamos Talk, 1987 March 16 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - International Geosphere - Biosphere Program - 3rd International Conference - Boulder, CO, 1988 May (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Education Talk, circa 1991 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Mathematical Ecology Workshop - Trieste, Italy, 1992 November (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - Aspen Global Change Insitute "Surprise and Global Environmental Change" (SHS w/ Billie L. Turner), 1994-1995 (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Aspen Global Change Institute, 1994 (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - "NBS Status and Trends" drafts [TLR and SHS], 1995 (Box 223, Folder 11)
  - Aspen Global Change Institute (AGCI), 1996 (Box 223, Folder 12)
  - Aspen Global Change Institute (AGCI) notes, 1996 (Box 223, Folder 13)
  - AGCI "Imaginable Surprise in Global Change Science" etc., 1996 (Box 223, Folder 14)
  - Global Climatic Change Conference - Employers Reinsurance Corporation, 1996 July (Box 223, Folder 15)
  - Teaching about Water Pollution Prevention Conference - Hayward, CA, 1996 October (Box 223, Folder 16)
  - Aspen Global Change Institute (AGCI), 1998 (Box 223, Folder 17)
  - Jefferson Institute / Fort Mason, 1999 July (Box 223, Folder 18)
  - Congressional Testimony - background materials, undated (Box 223, Folder 19)
  - EFIEA (European Forum on Integrated Environmental Assessment) Policy Workshop Series - "Strategic Cyclical Scaling: Bridging Five Orders of Magnitude Scale Gaps in Climatic and Ecological Studies" (TLR and SHS), 2000 July 12-19 (Box 223, Folder 20)
  - Annual Reviews: Energy and the Environment meeting, 2001 February (Box 223, Folder 21)
  - Center for Environmental Science and Policy (CESP) meeting, 2003 Jan 31 (Box 223, Folder 22)
  - Global Green Board meeting - New York, NY, 2003 October (Box 223, Folder 23)
  - TED - Monterey, CA, 2003 (Box 223, Folder 24)
  - Exeter - United Kingdom - Avoiding Dangerous Climate Change (1/2), 2005 Feb 1-3 (Box 223, Folder 25)
  - Exeter - United Kingdom - Avoiding Dangerous Climate Change (2/2), 2005 Feb 1-3 (Box 223, Folder 26)
  - SIIS (Stanford Institute for International Studies) - Bill Clinton Talk, 2005 May (Box 223, Folder 27)
  - Argentina and Chile trip itinerary, 2007 (Box 223, Folder 28)
  - World Wildlife Federation Climate Camp - contact list, brief info, 2008 (Box 223, Folder 29)
  - Making Your Presentation Memorable - Woods Institute for the Environment Workshop, 2008 June (Box 223, Folder 30)
  - Sustainability @ Stanford: Rising to the Challenge, 2008 Feb (Box 223, Folder 31)
  - Witness Statement of Dr. Schneider in Auckland re: M.J. (Jim) Salinger, 2009 (Box 223, Folder 32)
  - Summary of Data Elicited from Climate Experts (1/2), 1994 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Summary of Data Elicited from Climate Experts (2/2), 1994 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - AAAS (American Association for the Advancement of Science) - including letter from Margaret Mead (1/2), 1977 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - AAAS (American Association for the Advancement of Science) (2/2), 1977 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Aldo Leopold Fellows [communication] Training Program (1/2), 1999 June 17 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Aldo Leopold "Communicating Well in Challenging Situations" (2/2), 1999 June 17 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Aldo Leopold Training Program, 2000 June (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Developing a Research Agenda for Linking Ecological and Socioeconomic Systems, 2000 June 5-8 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change, 2000 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Handouts / Powerpoints from others' presentations (1/3), 2001 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - Handouts / Powerpoints from others' presentations (2/3), 2001 (Box 224, Folder 11)
  - Handouts / Powerpoints from others' presentations (3/3), 2001 (Box 224, Folder 12)
  - EMF (Energy Modeling Forum) Workshop on Climate Change Impacts and Integrated Assessment, 2001 July 30- August 3 (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - Handouts from EMF (1/3), 2001 (Box 224, Folder 14)
  - Handouts from EMF (2/3), 2001 (Box 224, Folder 15)
  - Handouts from EMF (3/3), 2001 (Box 224, Folder 16)
  - Millenium Ecosystem Assessment: Conceptual Framework Report (1/3), 2002 December (Box 224, Folder 17)
  - Millenium Ecosystem Assessment: Conceptual Framework Report (2/3), 2002 December (Box 224, Folder 18)
  - Millenium Ecosystem Assessment: People and Ecosystems (3/3), 2002 October (Box 224, Folder 19)
  - Aldo Leopold Leadership Program, 2002 (Box 224, Folder 20)
  - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change, 2004 (Box 224, Folder 21)
  - Global Warming: Science and Policy Issues - Poster for Nippon Paper Presentation, 2007 (Box 224, Folder 22)
  - The Global Commons, 1988 (Box 247, Folder 11)
  - International Conference on BioEvents, 1988 (Box 247, Folder 12)
  - An Energy Agenda for the 1990's (Box 247, Folder 13)
  - Chapman conference on the Gaia Hypothesis (AGU), San Diego, CA, 1988 (Box 247, Item 14-18)
  - National Forum on Partnerships Supporting Education about the Environment. ["National Forum on Partnerships Supporting Education about the Environment," a demonstration project of the President's Council on Sustainable Development, held at the Presidio, San Francisco, California, in the fall of 1994] (Item National Forum on Partnerships Supporting Education about the Environment, Box 250, Folder 7, Item not specified)
- Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), Series 7
  - Miscellaneous IPCC papers & memos, 1989-1995 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - IPCC/SAR WG1 5th Plenary Session Madrid, 1995 (Box 104, Item 2-5)
  - Drafts of editorials by Schneider et al, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - IPCC/SAR "Characterizing Scientific Uncertainty" draft (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Meeting materials UN Framework Convention on Climate Change (UNFCC), 1997 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - IPCC publications, 1995-1998 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Photocopies of various articles (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - IPCC/SAR miscellaneous documents (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - SAR/WG2 "Summary for Policymakers" final draft (Box 104, Item 12-16)
  - IPCC/SAR draft review sheets & 3rd drafting plan (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - IPCC/SAR scoping memos (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - IPCC/SAR drafts chapters 1- 11 + summary dated, 1995 Apr (Box 104, Item 19-21)
  - IPCC/SAR Table of contents & scoping meeting materials (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - Climate Change: Summary for Policymakers, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - IPCC/TAR various zero-order draft chapter samples (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - IPCC/TAR/WG2 Chapter 1 annotated draft (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - IPCC/TAR/WG2 Zero-order draft Chapter 2 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - IPCC/TAR/WG2 Zero-order draft Chapter 3 - Scenarious of impacts (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - IPCC/TAR/WG2 Zero-order draft Chapter 4 - Hydrology (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - IPCC/TAR/WG2 Zero-order draft Chapter 5 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - IPCC/TAR/WG2 Zero-order draft Chapters 7-10 + additional comments on chaps. 4-19 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - IPCC/TAR/WG2 Zero-order draft comments on chaps. 2-5, 18, 19 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to IPCC costing meeting (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - IPCC expert meeting on costing issue Tokyo, 6/29/1999 - 7/1/1999 (Box 105, Item 11-12)
  - IPCC/TAR comments on costing (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - New estimates of the damage costs of climate change by R.S.J. Tol, 1998 Apr (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Uncertainty paper with Richard Moss (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Uncertainty paper with photocopies of transparencies (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Uncertainty paper: drafts, comments, guidance for lead authors (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - "Uncertainties" 2nd draft for discussion (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - IPCC Special report on emissions scenarios - 1st order draft (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - SRES chapter 2 draft (Uncertainies) (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Interim characterizations of regional climate & related changes p to 2100/SRES TAR/WG2 guidance for lead authors (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - IPCC/TAR Cross cutting issues (X-Cut): guidance for authors, comments (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - IPCC/TAR Decision analysis framework (DAF) draft (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - IPCC/TAR Decision analysis framework (DAF): comments on paper (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Comments on Development, Equity, & Sustainability (DES) paper (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - IPCC workshop Helsinki, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - "Systems Thinking" + draft with annotations (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - Climate Change: Broad Consensus or "Scientific Cleansing?" by Schneider & Edwards (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - Lead authors meeting (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - IPCC/TAR miscellaneous articles (Box 105, Folder 30)
  - TAR/WG1 Final draft, Climate change:The Scientific Basis, 2001 (Box 106, Item 1-5)
  - TAR/WG1 Final draft, Summary for Policymakers, IPCC technical paper #4 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - TAR/WG2 schedules & meeting notes for writing teams (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - TAR/WG2 Final draft, Climate Change: Impacts, Adaptation, and Vulnerability (Box 106, Item 8-12)
  - TAR/WG3 Final draft, Climate Change: Mitigation, 2001 (Box 106, Item 13-16)
  - Synthesis Report to the Third Assessment Report (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - TAR/WG2 Synthesis Report: Summary for Policymakers (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - TAR/WG2 Technical summary (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - "Climate Change" by Robert T. Watson, photocopy of powerpoint presentation (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - "Climate Change and Biodiversity" by Robert T. Watson, photocopy of powerpoint presentation (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - IPCC technical paper #3 (photocopy) (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - TAR/WG2 Synthesis Report mapping document (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - TAR various working drafts (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - TAR Synthesis Report, various drafts with comments and revisions (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - TAR Synthesis Report, preliminary draft with notes & correspondence (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - TAR Synthesis Report, zero-order draft with notes & correspondence (Box 107, Item 5-11)
  - TAR Synthesis Report, zero-order draft with notes & comments (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - TAR Synthesis Report, zero-order draft with notes, comments, figures (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - TAR Synthesis Report, approved text & figures (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - TAR Synthesis Report, final government distribution report (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - TAR Government comments on Summary for Policymakers (SPM) of Synthesis Report (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - TAR Government comments on full text of Synthesis Report (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - TAR Expert comments on full text of Synthesis Report (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - TAR Synthesis Report: Summary for Policymakers, working drafts (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - TAR Synthesis Report: Summary for Policymakers, collated comments (Box 107, Folder 20)